let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does the acronym AES stand for?",
    answer: "Advanced Encryption Standard",
    options: [
      "Automated Encryption Strength",
      "Advanced Encryption Standard",
      "Algorithm Encrypted System",
      "Advanced Encryption Solution "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of a VPN (Virtual Private Network) in cyber security?",
    answer: "Encrypt and secure communication over the internet",
    options: [
      "Speed up internet connection",
      "Encrypt and secure communication over the internet",
      "Block malicious websites",
      "Boost Wi-Fi signal strength"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What type of software infects a machine, locks the files, then asks for money?",
    answer: "Ransomware",
    options: [
      "Worm",
      "Trojan",
      "Ransomware",
      "Browser Hijacker"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the purpose of a CAPTCHA in online security?",
    answer: "Preventing automated bots",
    options: [
      "Detecting malware",
      "Authenticating users",
      "Preventing automated bots",
      "Encrypting data"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of these groups exploit vulnerabilities?",
    answer: "All Of The Above",
    options: [
      "Governments",
      "Criminals",
      "Hacktivists",
      "All Of The Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is not a Cybercrime?",
    answer: "AES",
    options: [
      "Denial of Service",
      "Man in the Middle",
      "Malware",
      "AES"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of Cyber attack?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Phishing",
      "SQL Injections",
      "Password Attack",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which software is mainly used to help users detect viruses and avoid them?",
    answer: "Antivirus",
    options: [
      "Adware",
      "Malware",
      "Antivirus",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Identify the port used to connect to Active Directory in Windows 2000.",
    answer: "389",
    options: [
      "139",
      "445",
      "80",
      "389"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Choose among the following techniques, which are used to hide information inside a picture.",
    answer: "Steganography",
    options: [
      "Image rendering",
      "Steganography",
      "Rootkits",
      "Bitmapping"
    ]
  },
];
